{
  "author": "ramseyfox",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What 5-letter word is used for a female fox?",
      "answer": "Vixen"
    },
    {
      "question": "What Scottish chef stars in the Fox cooking competition 'Hell's Kitchen'?",
      "answer": "Gordon Ramsay,Ramsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "What British author's works include 'Matilda', 'The BFG', and 'Fantastic Mr. Fox'?",
      "answer": "Roald Dahl,Dahl"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the masked fox thief in 'Dora the Explorer'?",
      "answer": "Swiper"
    },
    {
      "question": "What Greek storyteller is credited with authoring fables such as 'The Tortoise and the Hare', 'The Boy Who Cried Wolf', and 'The Fox and the Grapes'?",
      "answer": "Aesop"
    },
    {
      "question": "Special Agents Fox Mulder and Dana Scully were the protagonists of what landmark sci-fi television show?",
      "answer": "The X-Files,The X Files,The XFiles,X-Files,X Files,XFiles"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jamie Foxx voices the lead role of jazz musician Joe Gardner in what 2020 Disney-Pixar animated afterlife film?",
      "answer": "Soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "Vicente Fox was elected president of which country in the Americas in 2000?",
      "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
      "question": "What 5-letter word meaning 'to move in a stealthy or sneaky manner' is the collective noun for a group of foxes?",
      "answer": "Skulk"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": ""
    }
  ]
}